

Grace Tao

gtao1@babson.edu

## **SUMMARY**

Open-minded, motivated and bilingual business student who has a multi-cultural background, and hopes to integrate business learning globally in the future. 3 years of experience in marketing. Seeking internship/eboard opportunity to develop marketing and public relations, leverage skills in Microsoft Excel, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe

## **SKILLS**

- \_ Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop

- Event Planning and Execution
- Internet and E-mail Marketing
- · Competitive and Trend Analysis

## **EXPERIENCE**

Hexapus

Boston, MA

Marketing Intern / Apr 2017 to Current

- Startup blogging company by Chinese international students that aims to provide tourist based strategy to help assist subscribers explore the great city of Boston
- · Conduct marketing advertising and public relations skills on social-media platform to extend company reputation
- Committed in composing weekly blogs for subscribers

Wavy

Wellesley Hills, MA

VP of Marketing/ Nov 2016 to Apr 2017

- Co-founded a non-profit, SEERS focused, start-up business with 11 other members which aimed to enhance customer shower experience with a goal to sustain water conservation
- Implemented marketing and growth strategy on the social media platforms such as Instagram and Facebook, and accomplished a profit margin of 54%
- Donated all profits to charity

**Dunkin Donuts** 

Wellesley, MA

Cashier/Server/ Sep 2016 to Current

- · Displayed well time-management skills by pursuing a part-time job while maintaining academic excellence
- Responsible for solving customer complaints which improved customer service learning
- Calculate total cash flow at the end of each shift

Hecom

Beijing, China

Marketing Research Intern/Jun 2015 to Aug 2015

- Analyzed major competitor Salesforce's marketing strategy to determine best practice for client relations and user experience.
- Conducted market research to identify Hecom's target audience
- Complied 4 weeks' worth of marketing research into a 3-hour long presentation, and delivered our analysis to Hecom's board of directors.

## EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Science: Business Administration

Babson College 2020

Wellesley, MA, US

Coursework includes Introduction to financial accounting, FME, QM for business analytics, Business Law., Managerial accounting, technology and operations, and microeconomics.